<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
<!-- Tenant Tab -->
	<TenantTurnedColonist>Colonist</TenantTurnedColonist>
	<Tenant>Tenant</Tenant>
	<Tenants>Tenants</Tenants>
	<FireFighting>FireFight</FireFighting>
	<FireFightingTip>Whether a tenant should help with fighting fires.</FireFightingTip>
	<FireFightingError>{PAWN_nameDef} won't fight fires!</FireFightingError>
	<Basic>Basic</Basic>
	<BasicTip>Whether a tenant should help with basic work like flicking.</BasicTip>
	<BasicError>{PAWN_nameDef} won't do basic work!</BasicError>
	<Hauling>Haul</Hauling>
	<HaulingTip>Whether a tenant should help with hauling.</HaulingTip>
	<HaulingError>{PAWN_nameDef} won't haul!</HaulingError>
	<Cleaning>Clean</Cleaning>
	<CleaningTip>Whether a tenant should help with cleaning.</CleaningTip>
	<CleaningError>{PAWN_nameDef} won't clean!</CleaningError>
	<MayJoin>May join</MayJoin>
	<MayJoinTip>Whether a tenant may request to join your colony permanently.</MayJoinTip>
	<Terminate>Terminate</Terminate>
	<TerminateTip>Terminate the contract early thus making the payment void.</TerminateTip>
	<AutoRenew>Auto renew</AutoRenew>
	<AutoRenewTip>Whether a tenant can automagically renew the contract at the expiry date.</AutoRenewTip>
	
	<!-- Mod Settings -->
	<MinDailyCost>The minimum a tenant must pay to stay daily: {0}</MinDailyCost>
	<MaxDailyCost>The maximum a tenant must pay to stay daily: {0}</MaxDailyCost>
	<MinContractTime>The minimum amount of days a contract entails: {0}</MinContractTime>
	<MaxContractTime>The maximum amount of days a contract entails: {0}</MaxContractTime>
	<StayChanceHappy>The chance a tenant will ask to prolong a contract if happy: {0}</StayChanceHappy>
	<StayChanceNeutral>The chance a tenant will ask to prolong a contract if satisfied: {0}</StayChanceNeutral>
	<LevelOfHappiness>The amount of happiness needed for a tenant to be considered happy: {0}</LevelOfHappiness>
	<TenantWeaponry>If a tenant may spawn with a weapon.</TenantWeaponry>
	<TenantApparel>If a tenant should spawn with less costly clothing.</TenantApparel>
	<SimpleClothingMax>The maximum amount a tenants clothing may be worth: {0}</SimpleClothingMax>
	<CourierCost>The cost for calling for courier services: {0}</CourierCost>
	<MinRelation>The minimum amount of relation change events and envoys gives: {0}</MinRelation>
	<MaxRelation>The minimum amount of relation change events and envoys gives: {0}</MaxRelation>
	<TenantRGB>Tenants RGB</TenantRGB>
	<AvailableRaces>The amount of races available for tenancy.</AvailableRaces>
	<Filter>Filter</Filter>
</LanguageData>